Colorado
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Colorado
2.1.1.1.4
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1175
- Colorado, 2.1.1.1.4
  - Stanley Hotel Manor and amusement hall, Estes Park, 1911; 20; 14000; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - In front of Stanley Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 21; 14001; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Stanley Hotel from hill opposite Estes Park, 1911; 22; 14003; 65; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Stanley Hotel music room, Estes Park, 1911; 23; 14005; 132; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Stanley Manor music room, Estes Park, 1911; 24; 1406; 136; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Stanley Manor music room, Estes Park, 1911; 25; 14007; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Bedroom, Stanley Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 26; 14010; 124; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Dining room, Stanley Manor, Estes Park, 1911; 27; 14011; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Hall in Stanley Manor, Estes Park, 1911; 28; 14012; 70; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Rocks near Stanley Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 29; 14014; 143; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Rocks behind Stanley Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 30; 14015; 74; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Fireplace in main building, Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 31; 14016; 9; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 32; 14017; 122; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Mill's house, Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 33; 14018; 126; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Rooms in Mrs. Sherman's cottage, Estes Park, 1911; 34; 14019; 128; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party at Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 35; 14020; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - "The Forest" at Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 36; 14021; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Porch of "the forest", Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 37; 14022; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Main building, Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 38; 14023; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Mr. Enos Mills, Estes Park, 1911; 39; 14024; 111; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Dorothy Schwartz, Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 40; 14025; 10; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Party at castle rocks, Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 41; 14027; 123; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Park on castle rocks, Long's PeaK, Estes Park, 1911; 42; 14027A; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Frank R. Roberson and party on castle rocks, near view, Estes Park, 1911; 43; 14028; 121; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Beaver dam, Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 44; 14029; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Beaver work on trees, Estes Park, 1911; 45; 14030; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Beaver dam near Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 46; 14031; 4; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Showing how a tree cured itself, Estes Park, 1911; 47; 14034; 150; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Mertensia orchid, lungwort, Estes Park, 1911; 48; 14035; 283; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Purple bell flower, clematis, Estes Park, 1911; 49; 14036; 282; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  - Lupinus, Estes Park, 1911; 50; 14037; 278; 5x7 (Box 1175)
  Box 1176
- Colorado, 2.1.1.1.4
  - Larkspur ans yellow orange flower, Estes Park, 1911; 1; 14041; 271; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Kinnikinick, Estes Park, 1911; 2; 14044; 265; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Potentilla climbing, Estes Park, 1911; 3; 14046; 269; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Pine cones, Estes Park, 1911; 4; 14047; 268; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Big Thompson Canyon, river and road, Estes Park, 1911; 5; 14064; 3; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Big Thomson Canyon, island in river, Estes Park, 1911; 6; 14065; 12; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Stream in Thompson Canyon, Estes Park, 1911; 7; 14066; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Bridge in Bid Thomson Canyon, Estes Park, 1911; 8; 14067; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Bridge in the canyon of the Big Thompson, Estes Park, 1911; 9; 14068; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Big Thomson Canyon, Estes Park, 1911; 10; 14069; 75; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Lyons Canyon road, Estes Park, 1911; 11; 14070; 66; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Route through Missouri Canyon, Estes Park, 1911; 12; 14072; 21; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Range from Rustic Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 13; 14073; 25; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Rustic Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 14; 14074; 2; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - General view of Estes Park, 1911; 15; 14075; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - General view of Estes Park, taken from mountain near entrance, 1911; 16; 14076; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Looking into Estes Park from mountain near entrance, 1911; 17; 14077; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Ypsilon mountain, Estes Park, 1911; 18; 14078; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Range from Park Hill, Estes Park, 1911; 19; 14079; 116; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Range from Park Hill, Estes Park, 1911; 20; 14080; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Range from Mr. Lanborn's house[?], Estes Park, 1911; 21; 14081; 61; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Mountain range, Long's Peak Inn to left Estes Park, 1911; 22; 14082; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Estes Park, 1911; 23; 14083; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Cabin in the woods, Estes Park, 1911; 24; 14084; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Cottages among trees, Estes Park, 1911; 25; 14085; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Deer mountain in the distance, Estes Park, 1911; 26; 14086; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Song's Peak, Estes Park, 1911; 27; 14087; 5x7 (Box 1176)
  - Beaver dam, Estes Park, 1911; 28; 14089; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - The fish hatchery, Estes Park, 1911; 29; 14090; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Trout in pond, Estes Park, 1911; 30; 14091; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Enos Mills feeding chipmunk, Estes Park, 1911; 31; 14092; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Frank R. Roberson and chipmunk, Estes Park, 1911; 32; 14093; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Mr. Enos Mills and a chipmunk, Estes Park, 1911; 33; 14094; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Mr. Lamborne and Bevis(dog), Estes Park, 1911; 34; 14095; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Lake and trees, Estes Park, 1911; 35; 14096; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Bevis(a dog), Estes Park, 1911; 36; 14097; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Bevis waiting for sugar, Estes Park, 1911; 37; 14098; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Children on horseback, Estes Park, 1911; 38; 14099; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Donkeys, Estes Park, 1911; 39; 14100; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Johnny Adam's cabin, Estes Park, 1911; 40; 14101; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Lamborne, Estes Park, 1911; 41; 14102; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Mr. Lester, proprietor of the Rustic Hotel, Estes Park, 1911; 42; 14103; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Johnny Adams, Estes Park, 1911; 43; 14104; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Fishing in Big Thompson Canyon, Estes Park, 1911; 44; 14105; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Canyon of the Big Thompson, Estes Park, 1911; 45; 14106; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Narrow defile[?], Big Thompson Canyon, Estes Park, 1911; 46; 14107; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Fisherman in the canyon of the Big Thompson, Estes Park, 1911; 47; 14108; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Fishing in the Big Thompson, Estes Park, 1911; 48; 14109; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Road and river,canyon of the Big Thompson, Estes Park, 1911; 49; 14110; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Trout fishing in Big Thompson, Estes Park, 1911; 50; 14111; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Flower, potentilla?, Estes Park, 1911; 51; 14112; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Blue bell flower, clematis douglasii, Estes Park, 1911; 52; 14113; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Flowers, erigeron (probably) poliospermum, Estes Park, 1911; 53; 14115; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  - Iris, missouriensis, Estes Park, 1911; 54; 14116; 4x5 (Box 1176)
  Box 1177
- Colorado, 2.1.1.1.4
  - Flowers, Estes Park, 1911; 1; 14117; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Flowers, Estes Park, 1911; 2; 14118; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Yellow flower, Estes Park, 1911; 3; 14119; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Range of mountains, Estes Park, 1911; 4; 14120; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Entrance to Estes Park, 1911; 5; 14121; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Long's Peak, Estes Park, 1911; 6; 14123; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Road to Mr. Mills, Estes Park, 1911; 7; 14124; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Road to Long's Peak Inn, Estes Park, 1911; 8; 14125; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Deer Mountain Drive, Estes Park, 1911; 9; 14126; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Road on Deer Mountain Drive, Estes Park, 1911; 10; 14127; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Lyon's Canyon Road, Estes Park, 1911; 11; 14128; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - School house, Estes Park, 1911; 12; 14129; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Balanced rock, Estes Park, 1911; 13; 14130; 4x5 (Box 1177)
  - Denver at night, showing electric building, 1911; 14; 14049; 5x7 (Box 1177)
  - Denver at night, showing auditorium, 1911; 15; 14050; 5x7 (Box 1177)
  - Denver at night, looking up the 16th Street, 1911; 16; 14051; 5x7 (Box 1177)
  - Denver at night, 1911; 17; 14052; 5x7 (Box 1177)
  - Denver at night, 1911; 18; 14053; 5x7 (Box 1177)
  - Main Street, Fort Collins, 1911; 19; 14054; 5x7 (Box 1177)
  - Bank Interior, Fort Collins, 1911; 20; 14055; 5x7 (Box 1177)
  - Lover's lane, Fort Collins, 1911; 21; 14056; 5x7 (Box 1177)
  - Residence, Fort Collins, 1911; 22; 14058; 5x7 (Box 1177)
  - Y.M.C.A., Fort Collins, 1911; 23; 14059; 5x7 (Box 1177)
  - Interior of Y.M.C.A., Fort Collins, 1911; 24; 14060; 5x7 (Box 1177)
  - Business section of town, Fort Collins, 1911; 25; 14061; 5x7 (Box 1177)
  - Street, Fort Collins, 1911; 26; 14062; 5x7 (Box 1177)
  - Agriculture college, Fort Collins, 1911; 27; 14063; 5x7 (Box 1177)